[reel-to-reel tape recorder creaking]
[static]
[Benjamin] This is Doctor Benjamin Price,
professor of ancient history,
log number four.
[inhales]
The fabled Necronomicon,
The Book of the Dead, is not just a myth.
The Circle of the Wise Men have found it.
And despite my warnings, they read
from the book's unholy passages,
unleashing flesh-possessing demons
so malevolent as though
the devil himself were here.
God help us.
[unsettling music playing]
Log number five.
We found something.
An item of great power.
Capable of sending them back to hell.
Should they return,
I have hidden it behind rune and hex.
It must remain that way...
[unsettling music continues]
...for if unsealed, they will sense it.
They will smell its call in the earth.
Taste it on the air.
And then, they will stop at nothing...
to destroy it.
[ominous music playing]
[man 1] I swear to God,
he jumps out of the window.
- And he's running down the street...
- [man 2] Fuck that.
- ...in his underwear like it's a fucking movie.
- Who the fuck just jumps out of a window?
[man 1 laughs]
I know. Just a stupid motherfucker.
- [phone ringing]
- Oh, my God. Don't tell me that's Emma, man.
- Don't answer that.
- What if it's an emergency?
Leo, it's not an emergency.
She's just freaking out
about this lake story.
Next time, please,
you leave your fucking phone in the car.
- Okay?
- Get off my dick, bro.
Come on. Let's get outta here.
[motor starts]
[phone continues ringing]
You gotta be kidding me.
[man 2] Come on. Don't answer the phone.
- I--
- Don't answer your fucking phone, Leo.
I swear to God, if you answer that shit,
I'm leaving.
Hold your ground, man!
[Leo] Hey, hey, babe.
- You fucking--
- [Leo] Baby, how's it going?
I was just about to call.
Yeah, we've just been out on the water...
[intense music playing]
[uneasy music playing]
[breathes shakily]
[thrilling music playing]
Leo!
[splashing]
[choking]
[gasping]
[reel creaking]
[thunder rumbling]
[man 2 gasping]
[screams]
[Leo] I'll see you tomorrow.
Love you too. Bye. Bye.
Jared! Let's get the fuck outta here.
Quit fucking around!
Jared!
[Jared screaming in distance]
[foreboding music playing]
[Jared] Help!
What the-- Jared!
[motor powers down]
Jared!
Jared, where are you?
[intense music playing]
Leo!
Help! Help!
[screaming]
[shouting]
- Help me!
- [grunting]
[shouting]
[bubbling]
[Leo grunts]
Oh, my God!
Fuck!
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
I got you, buddy.
I got you.
[yelping]
[breathing shakily]
[thunder rumbling]
[ominous music playing]
[breathes shakily]
[ominous music continues]
- [music stops]
- [creaking]
[Leo screams]
[gasping]
What the fuck?
[ominous music continues]
[ominous music intensifies]
[breathing shakily]
[bubbling]
[sizzling]
[shouting in pain]
[sizzling continues]
[frantic screaming]
[screaming in pain]
[water bubbling]
[Leo whimpering]
[eerie music playing]
[eerie music continues]
[cars whooshing]
[eerie music stops]
[engine revving in distance]
[upbeat music playing on car speakers]
[engine accelerating]
[TANAKA 2
by Joey Valence & Brae and Logic playing]
♪ I bring fire when a Pop-Tart pop out ♪
♪ Born from a volcano ♪
♪ I Drain Gang like a sink drain Drano ♪
♪ Uncanny, I'm goin' hammy ♪
♪ Hit a hundred-note streak, hit the whammy bar ♪
♪ I wrap tight like a Trojan ♪
♪ That woman is a bad omen ♪
Got a little something
for the birthday boy here.
- [Joseph] Wow.
- [Will] Okay.
- [Thya] Gorgeous!
- Here we go.
Gone a little overboard,
- but you deserve it, huh?
- [Alice] I love it.
- [Thya] Happy birthday!
- Yay! Happy birthday!
- Yay!
- [Will] Happy birthday, bro.
- I'll get us some more champagne. Betsy!
- Uh...
No, Alice, Alice, Alice.
[whistles]
Come here.
What was that?
Are you serious with that whistle?
No, I'm just playing, okay?
But you're not listening.
This is our third bottle.
Maybe we ought to just, you know,
- slow it down a little bit.
- Yeah, it's Joseph's birthday.
We can get a little drunk.
Okay, okay.
Good vibes only, okay?
Let's, um, open presents.
Joseph,
happy birthday, bro.
This is, uh-- It's from both of us.
[Joseph] You guys didn't need to do anything else.
[upbeat dance music playing]
Wow. Thank you, guys. This is...
Oh, it's... It's a pen.
Yeah, well, it's not just any pen.
That's a Belvoir.
These are, like, a thousand bucks.
- Yeah, more. But that is not the point.
- [stutters]
I wanted to get it so--
You know, to encourage you
to finally finish your book.
[Alice sighs]
That's not very subtle, babe.
Well, to be fair,
this is the fifth book that he's started--
Actually, it's the fourth, so--
- [man 2] That's the fourth?
- Yeah.
Shit, man. I'm sorry.
But if you look at Alice, with her pictures,
I mean, you know, they were fine.
Ever since I bought her that bad boy,
the difference has been incredible,
and sometimes I think
you just need a little nudge.
Yeah. Speaking of...
- And... Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta!
- Another one.
- [Alice chuckles]
- Okay.
- [Alice] Happy birthday.
- [Joseph] I love the wrapping.
- [Thya gasps] No shit!
- [Joseph] Oh, my God.
- [Alice] Yeah!
- [woman 2] You look so cute!
Everybody looks cute
in black and white.
You didn't tell me
you were bringing your own gift.
- It's just a small something.
- Yeah.
Nothing compared to your Belvoir.
Our Belvoir.
I just said that it was from both of us.
Thank you, both. Thank you.
No, you're so talented.
- Oh--
- Oh!
[both chuckle]
I always forget.
You Americans like to hug.
The sister-in-law side hug.
Trying to kiss my boyfriend?
What's going on?
Well, you know, we French girls
like to give hand jobs when we say hello.
- Yeah, that's really classy.
- [chuckles]
Yeah. Talk about subtle, Alice.
He's just upset
because I brought my own gift.
[Will] What the fuck are you talking about?
I couldn't care less.
[Alice] So why are you criticizing everything?
- [Thya] I'm not criticizing, but ease up on the drinking.
- [Alice] Yes, you are.
- We're celebrating, of course I'm drinking.
- I know we're celebrating.
Just fucking tone it down!
Okay.
I'm done.
- Cigarette?
- [woman 2] Mmm-hmm.
Promise me we'll never get married, okay?
[dance music playing]
Look, dude, she-- she didn't mean anything by it.
No, no, no, no, she-- she meant it. Yeah, yeah.
She does this to rile me up.
It's like this cigarette thing.
We're talking about having a kid
and she refuses to stop. It's ridiculous.
[puffing]
It's ridiculous.
Let it go. You know what he's like.
Um... Can I bum a cigarette, boss?
Mike, enough. I'm not your boss.
I just send out the checks.
You are the boss. Come on.
Aren't you freezing to death in that T-shirt?
[Mike] Nah, feels great.
It's an oven in there.
Plus, the music is way too loud.
- [Alice] Yeah, I keep telling him that.
- [Mike] Mmm.
Yeah? No, go on,
continue to talk shit about me to my staff.
[Mike] We-- We're just talking.
[Will] It's cool, Mike. I know it's not you.
Alice, would you come back in, please?
Okay. Come here.
- [Alice] Don't touch me!
- Hey, hey, hey, okay.
Just relax.
Don't make me out to be someone
that I'm not, all right?
You're the one making a scene at my club.
And you make me out
to be this hysterical drunk.
[Will] Hey, I'm sorry, all right?
Now come on, let's go.
- [sighs]
- [Will] Hey, look at me.
Fuck, I just hate when you
act like a fucking child.
Don't call me that.
Just fucking cut it out with this shit.
Don't touch me! I told you!
[Will] Fuck! [grunts]
See, you bring this out in me.
Yeah, I was never this way before, Alice.
None of my exes
ever, ever made me blow up like this.
Why do you think that is?
If we can't talk,
then how do you expect
to move forward, huh?
Huh?
[Alice speaking indistinctly]
Yeah, sure, run back to Mike.
Why don't you give him another cigarette?
How about a hand job too?
Go to hell!
[muffled dance music playing]
[Thya] Joe...
- Hey, no, Will.
- Will, please, you're drunk.
Give me the keys. I'll drive you home.
Will!
[engine revving]
Fucking bitch.
[engine accelerating]
[radio static]
[indistinct chatter on radio channel]
[brakes screech]
[Will yelps]
[Will grunting]
[shouts]
[unsettling music playing]
[wheel creaking]
[indistinct chatter continues on radio channel]
[radio chatter continues]
[creaking]
[breathes shakily]
[unsettling music continues]
[woman whimpering]
Hey, hey, hey. Don't move. Don't...
move.
[woman continues whimpering]
I'll call 911.
I'll call...
Fuck.
[Will grunting]
- Fuck!
- [Jessica] Will?
[breathing shakily]
[Jessica] Will?
[thrilling music playing]
[in eerie voice]
We found you.
[breathes shakily]
Now lead us to your family.
[screaming]
What the fuck? [gasping]
[thrilling music continues]
Kunda.
[thrilling music intensifies]
Astratta.
[choking]
Fuck.
[Will grunting]
Montosse.
[yelps]
[shouting]
Help! Help me! Help!
Help!
Help! Help!
Canda.
[whooshing]
[Will screaming]
Help!
- [sinister laugh]
- [Will continues screaming]
[sinister laugh continues]
[Will screaming]
[sinister laugh intensifies]
[sinister music playing]
[music fades]
[Alice in French]
[Alice's father in French]
[distant indistinct chatter]
[Thya in English]
Are you taking anything for sleep?
Hmm?
None of it really works.
When did you guys get in?
[Thya] Couple of days ago.
Joseph sort of lives here now.
His parents basically gave him
the vacation home.
Look up.
Since when do you have a gun?
That is not mine.
[chuckles softly]
It's Joseph's.
[whispers]
I think he wants to feel badass.
- Joseph? Badass?
- [both laugh]
It's cute. [chuckles]
[Susan breathes deeply]
[Alice] Hi, Polly. How are you?
[Susan] She won't remember you.
But it's only been a year, though.
[chuckles softly]
[Susan] We must be the same size.
[loud drilling]
- [dog whimpering]
- [gasps softly]
[in French]
[whistles]
[in English] Do you think that
with the construction, that we can--
[manager] No, no, don't worry.
They promised me they would stop at noon,
and they should be wrapping up
any minute now.
- We're gathered here--
- [loud drilling in distance]
[in loud voice] We're gathered here today
to celebrate the life of William Price.
To pay tribute,
and to share memories of him,
because for as long as
those memories live on...
[loud drilling continues]
...William will always be with us.
I would now like to ask Mrs. Susan Price,
William's mother,
to please share a few words.
Bonnie, what are you doing?
No, that's Susan, Grandma.
- Aunt Bonnie isn't with us--
- [Edgar] Don't waste your breath on her.
[distant drilling continues]
William.
My sweet boy.
I could go on for hours
about what an amazing child he was.
A model teenager.
And a man who made us so, so proud.
He was so enamored with French cuisine
that when he studied in Paris,
he surprised us
by bringing home a French wife. Alice.
Will dreamed of starting a family.
[loud drilling in distance]
[voice breaking] You two would have made
such outstanding parents.
[Susan sniffles]
And we could have been
Grandpa Edgar and Grandma Susan.
I would give anything
for us to be together again.
[manager] Thank you, Susan.
And, um, I'm very sorry about the... the noise.
[clears throat]
[sighs] Alice.
Would you like to share something with us?
A special memory of your husband?
I-- I didn't prepare a speech.
Oh...
Okay, um... Wow. Uh...
So...
I would like to play a song
that held a-- a special place in William's heart.
Your wedding song.
[La chanson des vieux amants
by Jacques Brel playing]
[singing in French]
[imperceptible]
[singing continues]
[music stops]
[coffin clattering]
[door slams]
[Hallehova by Sliim Bambino playing]
♪ I want the money, I want the car ♪
- ♪ I want your woman be telling me I'm a star ♪
- [sings along]
♪ And for the rest of it, homie, I pray to God ♪
♪ I'm yelling hovah ♪
♪ Halle, halle, hallehovah ♪
♪ Hovah ♪
♪ Halle, halle, halle ♪
♪ What ♪
♪ What these bitches want when they spend ♪
♪ About a dozen summers gettin' real dope ♪
♪ Where they're lookin' at my Twitter
When I have these lil' hoes ♪
♪ Livin', spittin' like
They think they real pros ♪
♪ With the quote fingers
Hear me, though ♪
♪ I can smell a fraud like a dog do ♪
♪ Talkin' whether it be summer, autumn,
But they fall through ♪
♪ Sue me if you think you got it better with the boss, fool ♪
♪ This is real rap, motherfucker,
This ain't law school ♪
♪ I just lost a friend on some pill shit... ♪
- [music fades]
- [pounding on door]
- [buzzing]
- [fire hisses]
[music continues on earphone]
I'd like to say goodbye to my son
one last time.
Um, well...
You-- You'll be able to collect the ashes
in a couple of days,
- but you're not actually allowed back here.
- Sir.
My son just died.
Five minutes.
And don't tell anyone or I'll get yelled at.
Thank you.
My condolences.
[somber music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[sobs]
[continues sobbing]
[knock on door]
[distant thumping]
[uneasy music playing]
[crackling]
- [loud thud]
- Fuck! [gasps]
Will! Will!
[intense music playing]
Hang on! Hang-- Hang on!
Uh... Will! I'm coming!
Will! Hold on, son!
[shouting]
I'm coming! Fuck.
[grunting]
- [sizzling]
- [Edgar yelling]
[grunting]
[Edgar groans]
[intense music continues]
What the fuck?
[man screaming]
Help! Help!
[haunting music playing]
[haunting music continues]
- [music stops]
- [horn honking]
- Come with us.
- Okay.
- Okay. We'll see you there.
[horn continues honking]
[Alice sighs]
How far is it?
[whispers] Damn.
[Thya] Less than five minutes away.
[Alice groans] Fucking...
You okay?
Yeah, no, it's just...
You know they don't want me there.
That's not true.
Kit, in here.
Yeah.
[chuckles softly] Jesus.
[Thya giggles]
All right, look. The only thing
they care about is that we're all together.
You're part of the family.
Even my mom.
I mean, she said that she was really touched
you agreed to the cremation
instead of the burial,
and we could do it where she wanted.
[chuckles softly]
She appreciates you. Honestly.
Yeah, maybe. I don't know.
Well, I mean, my dad, on the other hand,
I mean, he can't fucking stand you.
- [chuckles]
- [Thya] Oh, God.
[unsettling music playing]
[Alice] Looks so run-down now.
[Thya] Wait, you've been here before?
[Alice] We got married here.
[haunting music playing]
Mom? Dad?
Be right back.
Grandma. You know where Mom is?
Oh.
She's still at school. It lets out at four.
Yeah. Thank you.
Mom?
[overhead clattering]
- What are you doing?
- What do you think?
You invited Alice.
She was Will's wife.
Here, Mom, let me do this.
When we gave you this place,
I asked you to throw everything away.
Why are his things still here?
I just wanted to keep something from Grandpa.
It felt like I was throwing him away.
He threw us away.
[Joseph] No, I know. It's just...
I mean, some of this stuff,
it's fascinating, you know?
[Benjamin] Unleashing flesh-possessing demons
so malevolent as though
the devil himself were here.
[clicks]
Does that sound fascinating to you?
It's just inspiration for my book.
Your book is about Grandpa?
No, not him.
His research. I mean...
[scoffs]
Come on. Curses, and demons...
I found all kinds of crazy artifacts
he brought back from around the world,
and apparently he was
part of some secret society.
It was a cult.
[Joseph] They were historians, you know.
And he recorded everything in his notebook.
Look, I was gonna tell you.
[Susan] No, let me tell you.
- My father was not a good man, Joseph.
- Mom--
When my mom's mind started to go, he retreated.
Spent more time with
the Circle of the Wise Men than us.
Always off on some expedition,
buried in some stupid old book.
When Aunt Bonnie got sick,
that's when he left us for good.
Hunting for rusty weapons.
Crumbling scrolls.
He said he had to find a way
to protect us from evil.
All he ever did was talk like that
because he didn't have the courage
to face real hardship.
[inhales]
I had to take care of this family.
I'm sorry, Mom.
- You should get some rest.
- It's fine.
I'm fine. It's the pills.
Tell everyone lunch in an hour.
Throw this out.
[Polly yelling]
- Let go of me!
- What's going on?
- She insists on going outside by herself.
- [Polly] No!
- [yelling] No!
- [grunts]
- [Thya] What are you doing, Polly?
- [Joseph] Grandma!
I was just trying to help!
Bonnie! Bonnie!
I've got her. She's trying to steal my money.
- [Thya] Polly!
- [Polly] Call the police!
- Susan, we were just trying--
- [Polly] Let go of me.
[Polly] Bonnie!
- [Joseph] Grandma, are you okay?
- [Susan] Calm down.
- [Polly] It's broken.
- Just a sec, Mom.
You thief.
Oh, my God.
- [pull start rattles]
- [Edgar coughing]
[Edgar coughs hoarsely]
Dad?
[metallic clank]
[Edgar continues coughing]
[pull start rattling]
[Joseph] Dad.
[unsettling music playing]
[motor whirring powerlessly]
It's out of gas.
[rattling]
[Edgar breathing heavily]
You don't need to worry about the yard.
[Edgar] Someone's gotta do it.
- I will, I just haven't had--
- We leave you this house...
[inhales] ...and you let it rot.
You like living in shit!
[Edgar coughing]
[continues coughing]
[male voice] Dad.
Dad. Help me.
[uneasy music playing]
[ghostly voice 1] We're inside.
[ghostly voices echoing]
- [ghostly voice 2] Let us in, Dad.
- [grunts]
It's okay.
[ghostly voice 2] Don't fight.
[haunting music playing]
Come on, you can do it.
[echoing] Do it.
Do it. Do it.
[distant rattling]
[Alice] Edgar?
Edgar, are you okay?
- [gasps]
- [glasses shattering]
No, no!
[Edgar grunting]
[both gasp]
[Alice breathing heavily]
[Alice gasps]
Don't tell my wife.
- Please.
- [breathing heavily]
I'll hold onto this, okay?
[Edgar] Mmm.
[timer ratcheting]
[door creaks]
- What happened?
- [Alice] Uh...
I missed a step in the cellar.
I dropped the plates. I'm sorry.
[Susan] Yes, I heard that.
Would you put this on the dining room table?
Please be careful with it.
[inhales] Made it myself.
You did?
It's Niobe.
- A Greek queen.
- [Alice gasps softly]
- She's Edgar's favorite.
- [Alice] It's pretty.
Yeah.
Why did you stop?
First, the kids.
Then my sister Bonnie got sick.
[whispers]
And my mother couldn't live on her own.
Well...
You had a gift. It's a shame.
Why is it a shame?
I was with the people I love.
Building a life.
You know, without my family, I'm nothing.
[joyful chatter on video]
[cameraman] Testing.
[both laughing]
[chuckles softly]
[Max whimpering]
[chatter continues on video]
[Susan] Thank you, Joseph.
That was beautiful.
[Edgar coughing]
- [Max whimpering]
- [Edgar continues coughing]
You okay?
[Edgar] Mmm.
I'm good.
[Edgar coughs]
No.
That's Will's seat.
[Polly] Oh. My big boy, Will.
When does he get here?
- [table clatters]
- [Max whimpers]
[chair scraping]
Edgar. Would you do the wine, please?
[Edgar] Mmm.
[Edgar grunts softly]
Oh, don't worry. I got it.
[exhales]
[Joseph] Mmm, so good.
They're premade. I just heated them.
Joseph is right, they're... they're delicious.
I would never guess it was frozen.
That's concerning.
Hmm?
It's clearly frozen food on paper plates.
If you manage the restaurant alone,
you'll need to know frozen from fresh.
- [cork pops]
- [Alice] Mmm.
About the restaurant...
I'm-- I'm not sure I plan to...
Let's just talk about it another time.
- Let's talk about it now.
- [soft tense music playing]
- We're all here.
- [Max whimpers]
Well, I haven't decided anything,
but, I mean, it was Will's restaurant--
You ran the place together.
I only did the accounting.
But you're... his wife.
You sure?
[Alice] To be honest, I-- I was thinking,
I might go back to Paris for a while.
Maybe stay with my... with my dad.
Then things seem
a little more decided than you let on.
No, no, no.
These things should be dealt with
as a family.
Yeah.
- We should deal with it as a family.
- [whimpers]
[Susan] You know the staff adores you.
Alice, they need you.
Think about Will. Do it for him.
Wait, I recognize you.
You're married to my grandson, aren't you?
Don't turn a deaf ear.
I asked you a question.
It's all right. [shushes]
- I--
- It's okay. It's okay.
All I'm saying is
you have the chance
to take over a successful business
while honoring Will at the same time.
It was his life's work.
It was his passion.
And you should carry it on.
Susan, I really think
we should do this another time.
No, now's the best time
to lay everything on the table.
- [Susan] He's right.
- [soft tense music continues]
- We need to make decisions together.
- You are driving me fucking crazy!
Without me you are nothing, Alice.
- It's what Will would have wanted.
- [Edgar] That's Will's seat.
- That's your fucking problem!
- [Susan] Do it for him.
[Polly] Will. When does he get here?
We're trying to have a fucking kid!
You do not know what you fucking want!
Say it.
Don't you fucking bait me, Alice.
- [distorted warbling]
- [splashes]
Alice!
Please, calm down.
I am calm.
But you shouldn't speak on Will's behalf.
I'm his mother.
No one knows him better than I do.
[Polly slurping]
[Joseph] Grandma, no.
[stops slurping]
Sorry. Okay, look.
We're all here for him,
but I-- I think Alice is right.
- This isn't the right time to--
- It's never the right time for you, is it?
[uneasy music continues]
That's why you've done nothing
with your life.
Edgar. Please.
- Don't you fucking touch me.
- Edgar,
we're all grieving here,
but that's no reason to be cruel.
- Thya, it's fine.
- It's not.
- Joe...
- Where is it?
[soft tense music playing]
Where's the wedding ring?
Why aren't you wearing it?
Did you sell it?
[Max whimpering]
- You get a good price?
- No! No, no, of course not.
- I...
- Edgar, can I have the corkscrew, please?
[Max whimpering]
[Edgar] And a hoodie and sneakers
at her husband's funeral.
I'm right here, Edgar.
You can speak to me directly.
You didn't even cry.
Don't you think that's weird?
People grieve in different--
- [Edgar] Get away from me!
- [Max squealing]
[Max whimpering]
[coughs]
[huffing]
[Edgar] Will's dead.
And now you inflict this on us?
That's enough.
Dad. You don't look good--
It's your fault he's dead.
[unsettling music playing]
You didn't stop him getting to the car!
Stop it, Dad. I had nothing to do with it.
Will got into a fight with Alice, and he--
What? Are you implying it was my fault?
- No, no, of course not.
- You were there.
You couldn't stop him
from getting in the car either.
[Joseph] I know. Alice, I know, I tried.
- [Alice] We tried. Okay, I didn't.
- [Max whimpers]
- That doesn't mean it's my fault.
- That's not what I'm saying--
- This is exactly what you said.
- [Joseph] Alice, no.
- Alice, I think--
- [Alice] No. I think
you should all mind your own business.
You don't know anything.
[Max whimpering]
You're glad he's dead.
Please, please, please.
Will's looking down on us from above.
From above?
He's down below.
[Max whimpering]
- [grunts]
- [continues whimpering]
- [shouting]
- [Max yelping in pain]
Stop!
[Edgar grunts]
[Joseph] The dog!
- [panting]
- [Edgar] Help me.
[gasping in fright]
Help me.
Help me!
- Get your keys.
- Okay.
[Thya] Let's take him to the hospital!
[Joseph] Thya! I need help! Grab his arm!
[Thya] I got him! I got him!
What did we do to deserve this?
[door slams]
They left without saying goodbye.
[suspenseful music playing]
Jesus fucking Christ, is he fucking crazy?
Thya, please. Give me a second.
- He killed your fucking dog!
- I know!
[Joseph panting]
Shit, shit.
He's fucking bleeding everywhere. Shit.
[panting]
Shit, shit. Come on!
[Joseph breathing heavily]
[foreboding music playing]
[Thya] Joe?
- [Joseph] What?
- Your dad.
[tense music playing]
[yelps]
- No! No!
- [Edgar grunts]
[Joseph] No!
- [grunts]
- [Thya yelps]
[Thya gasping]
[music stops]
[tires screech in distance]
[tense music continues]
[Edgar grunting]
[Thya whimpering, screaming]
[Edgar growls]
[grunting]
[gasping]
- [Edgar grunts]
- [Joseph groans]
- [screaming]
- [Joseph] What the fuck?
[muffled screaming]
[Joseph] Oh, my fucking God.
- [gasps] Oh, my God!
- [Joseph grunting]
- [Edgar growling]
- [grunting]
[screaming]
[groaning]
[gasps]
[Joseph] Stop!
Let her go! [pants]
- [Thya] Shoot him!
- I said let her go!
Fucking shoot him!
[Thya choking]
[gasping]
[Edgar in eerie voice] Shoot me, Joe.
Shoot me.
[Thya gasping]
Shoot me, Joe!
Shoot me!
[Joseph and Thya yelling]
[Edgar growling]
[Joseph and Thya continue yelling]
[Edgar grunting]
[Joseph shouts]
[muffled shouting]
[breathing heavily]
[growling]
[Thya screams]
[Edgar growling]
[gasps]
Joseph!
[groaning]
- [grunts]
- [Edgar growling]
[breathing heavily]
[haunting music playing]
[imperceptible screaming]
[music fades]
[shovel clanking]
[sighs]
[mysterious music playing]
[Alice] "October, 1983.
That cursed Book of the Dead.
I warned them against reading from it.
The forbidden incantation.
Four words that can unleash evil.
But they didn't listen.
December, 1983.
At last, I have found it.
A weapon that can stop them all.
A dagger created by
the Circle of the Wise Men.
The tiniest cut from this ancient blade
rips their demonic souls from their bodies.
I've hidden it, but now must leave again.
These creatures are hunting me
and I must protect my wife and daughters."
[exhales]
[mysterious music continues]
[ghostly voices echoing]
"Kunda."
[foreboding music playing]
[music stops]
"Astratta."
[foreboding music continues]
[music stops]
[ghostly voices echoing]
[gulps]
"Montosse."
[foreboding music continues]
Fuck this.
[foreboding music playing]
- [glass shatters]
- [Alice screams] Get away!
- [growling]
- [screaming continues]
[barking]
[whimpering]
[grunts]
[distant thump]
Alice?
[mumbling]
What's wrong?
[mouthing in French]
[in English]
I don't understand you.
[Joseph panting]
[Susan] What happened?
[panting continues]
Where's your father?
[shakily]
I think Dad just killed Thya.
[knocks on door]
[ominous music playing]
[knocking continues]
[Thya] Open up. It's me.
She came back for my money.
[woman choking]
[ominous music continues]
[door creaks, closes]
[Susan gasps]
[eerie music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[bone cracks]
[in eerie voice]
To your perfect family.
Cheers.
[sizzling]
[gurgling]
- [Thya growls]
- [Susan grunts]
[Alice grunts]
[Joseph groans]
[Joseph and Alice grunting]
[metallic clank]
[intense music playing]
[Susan sobbing]
[Joseph grunts]
[Thya yells]
- [bone cracks]
- [Thya yelps]
[panting]
Joe, it hurts.
- Please, Joe.
- Joe!
[door slams]
[muffled screaming]
- [Susan] Where is your father?
- [Joseph] We gotta go.
We gotta go. Alice! Alice, come on!
Come on, we gotta go!
[Alice breathing heavily]
[foreboding music playing]
[music stops]
Edgar.
- Sweetheart.
- Susan, don't.
- Get off me!
- Mom!
[foreboding music continues]
[whistles]
[breathes shakily]
[Polly whimpers]
[Susan breathing shakily]
[in eerie voice]
You should be dead.
Not Will.
- No!
[eerie music playing]
[whimpering]
[imperceptible screaming]
[gas hissing]
[high-pitched ringing]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [gas hissing]
- [Joseph panting]
[panting]
[sighs]
[suspenseful music continues]
[panting]
[Joseph sighs]
[sighs] He's just standing there.
Staring.
[Alice] We're fucking trapped!
[Susan] I'll be right back, Mom.
[door opens]
[wood creaking]
[footsteps in the distance]
[banging on door]
[banging continues]
[breathes nervously] Ch--
Ch-- Children?
[banging continues]
[suspenseful music swelling]
Please.
Open the door.
Did you come back
to return what you stole?
Uh...
Oh.
Exactly.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Polly screams in the distance]
- [whimpering]
- [Susan] Oh, my God, Mom! Mom.
Are you okay?
Mom? Are you okay?
It's okay, I got you.
You're okay. It's okay.
[Thya in eerie voice] We will destroy it.
We will destroy it.
No more wise men.
Should-- Should I go,
or do-- do you wanna?
You go.
Get Grandma upstairs.
[breathes shakily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathing shakily]
- [electricity crackles]
- [panting]
[shaky breathing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[whimpers]
[in eerie voice] You thought
I'd let you have all the men
in this family to yourself?
[both screaming]
Joseph, come!
[Thya and Alice grunting, screaming]
[growling]
Help.
Don't bother, babe.
That's not his style.
I said come!
[gasps, pants]
Susan.
Stop coddling the boy.
He has something that we need.
- [Susan screaming]
- [Joseph] No! No!
[glass breaking]
[Joseph screams]
Give us what we came for!
- [machine beeping]
- [distant, muffled scuffling]
I told you she was a thief!
[tense music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[electric knife whirring]
Oh, so you're brave now?
Boo.
[Joseph screams]
[gasping]
[whimpers]
[haunting music playing]
[Joseph groans]
[grunts]
I was your first.
And I'll make sure I'm your last.
[Joseph screams]
[laughing]
[grunts]
So you wouldn't shoot your father.
But killing me...
is easy?
[low, menacing giggle]
[Polly] Come here, young lady!
I have what you want!
[stifled screaming]
[grunts]
Be right back, baby.
[gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
The money's under my mattress.
Take it, and leave us alone.
Aw.
It's all broked in here.
But there is something that we want
in that little head of yours.
Your husband must have told you
where it is.
Huh?
[humming]
Mmm.
- [dentures clack]
- Boop.
This will fix you.
[whimpers softly]
Polly.
Where's your leg?
[faint clank in the distance]
- That little--
- [Joseph grunts angrily]
The Circle of the Wise Men failed.
Your grandpa failed.
- You'll all die tonight.
- [grunts]
[grunting]
- [eerie music playing]
- [thudding]
[screams]
[panting, sobbing]
[Joseph panting]
[sobbing]
[Will in eerie voice] Alice. Alice. Alice.
I'm coming, Alice.
I'm coming for you.
Fucking say it!
[somber music playing]
[Alice] Joe.
What's the Circle of the Wise Men?
I didn't think that it was real.
Please stop hiding stuff,
and just tell me.
I saw those fucked up drawings
you threw out.
Did Will ever tell you
about our grandfather?
[sentimental music playing]
Growing up, we were always told
he was unstable.
In his journals, he described it as
this group convinced
the devil had been here.
And would return if anyone
read from what he called...
The Book of the Dead.
[dramatic music playing]
My grandfather left his family
to travel the world,
researching and collecting artifacts
as protection from all this.
You still have them?
My mom asked me to throw everything
away after he died, but...
- Fucking--
- No, no no.
She asked, but I didn't.
There's still some stuff
hidden up in the attic.
And Thya,
that thing inside her,
said they were looking for something.
Maybe whatever that is,
it can stop them.
[music stops]
Mom? I need you to drink this, please.
[glass thuds]
Can you look under the bed?
Daddy always checks
to make sure there aren't any monsters.
No monsters.
You're lying.
Don't worry.
You're safe here.
Goodnight, Mom.
[Polly] Goodnight, Susan.
What did you call me?
[Polly] Come, sweetheart.
[sobs]
Mom.
I missed you.
[sobbing] I missed you so much.
[gasps]
We share the same dream.
It can still come true.
The whole family can be reunited.
Will's already on his way.
He'll be here soon.
[shaky breathing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Don't be scared, Susan.
[knocking on door]
Remember what you said at the funeral.
[in eerie voice]
That you would give everything you have
for us all to be together again.
[Susan sobbing]
Without your family, you're nothing.
[in eerie voice] I miss you.
I miss us.
[dramatic music playing]
[Susan sighs]
[gasps]
You haven't kissed me
like that in years.
Your father's not there anymore.
Maybe we can-- [screams]
[Max barking]
[Susan] Joseph?
Hey, is-- is Grandma okay? Everything good?
Yes, everything's better now.
I need you to trust me.
Trust you?
They're not our enemies.
I realize that now.
They just want something back
that my father stole.
I told you, he was a bad man.
It's simple.
Tell them where it is.
Give them what they want, and this ends.
We can be happy again.
Where what is?
A weapon.
[tense music playing]
But we threw everything away.
You're lying to me.
Tell us where it is.
Us?
Where is the Kandarian dagger?
[dramatic music playing]
No! No!
- [Joseph] Alice! Alice, run!
- [object clattering]
[Susan] Leave us alone!
[Alice sobbing]
You need to stop meddling
in our family affairs.
You promised!
You promised not to hurt him!
[growling]
Finally some use
for this revolting piece of shit.
- [screams]
- [Edgar grunts]
Come.
See what you did.
[grunts]
[whimpering]
Finally, something you can be proud of.
[muffled screaming]
[stifled, indistinct speech]
[groans]
Did you say something?
I know where the dagger is! [sobbing]
Nothing will stand in our way now.
Once we have the dagger--
[Joseph] No!
[Susan] Get off him!
Get off him!
- [Susan] Edgar! Get off!
- [groans] Fuck.
[Joseph screams]
[whimpering]
[Susan screams]
[Alice gasping]
[Susan screaming]
- [Susan] Get off me!
- [objects clattering]
[gasping]
[Susan screams]
Help me! Help me!
[sobbing]
[screams]
[grunts]
[Susan] Get off me!
[distant, muffled scuffling]
[sobbing]
[dishes shattering]
[Joseph] No! No!
[Edgar growls]
[Joseph grunts]
[sobbing]
- [distant, muffled scuffling]
- [Joseph screaming, grunting]
[sobbing]
[objects shattering, thudding]
[wood creaking]
- [Alice squeals]
- [Edgar] Where's the dagger?
Where is it?
Answer me!
[Joseph] Find it.
Before them.
[screams]
[Joseph] No!
[objects shattering in the distance]
[muffled footsteps]
[hinges creaking]
[sobbing faintly]
[panting]
[ominous music playing]
[breathing deeply]
[motor revving]
[dramatic music playing]
[Max barking]
[breathing shakily]
[whimpers]
[glass crunches]
[gurgling]
[strangled shriek]
Oh, stop.
I'm just giving you what you want.
I know you liked it when Will hurt you.
Isn't that why you stayed?
[Alice panting]
Don't turn a deaf ear.
I asked you a question.
[Alice whimpering]
[sobbing]
[panting]
[grunts, screaming]
[high-pitched ringing]
Susan.
Help.
[Polly] Susan, dear.
Would you mind pushing the throttle
to tear this bitch's face off, please?
She brought chaos into this family.
Your son died because of her.
Do it.
- [grunts]
- [Polly] For Will.
[Alice sobbing]
Do it!
[breathes sharply]
[Polly] Do it!
Oh, Susan.
Do it.
I'm sorry, Alice.
[Alice yells]
[screams, groans]
[chair lift beeping]
[Alice sobbing]
[pants]
[sniffles, whimpers]
[groans]
[panting]
[high-pitched ringing]
[stifled screaming]
[gasping]
[high-pitched ringing]
[sobs]
[dramatic music playing]
[screams]
Is it Joseph?
Is it my son?
[Susan sobs]
[Susan groans]
[dramatic music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[Alice in French]
- [growling]
- [Alice panting]
[grunts]
- [banging on door]
- [Susan breathing heavily]
[doorknob rattling]
[Susan groans wearily]
[both groan in pain]
[breathing heavily]
[in English] What are you doing?
[Alice in French]
[in English] You should be grateful
I didn't leave you back there.
- [groans]
- [Alice] Don't you dare move.
Grateful?
[sighs]
[unsettling music playing]
[Alice groans]
My family is gone.
[sighs]
Everyone I love is gone.
Because of you.
All you've ever done is bring us pain.
- [screams]
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [clang]
- [Alice gasps]
I hate you.
Oh, shut up, Susan!
Shut the fuck up!
I didn't bring anything to your family.
It was already there.
You see this?
You see, Susan? This is your son.
This is what he was capable of.
- Was an accident!
- No! It wasn't!
[sobbing] It was not. And you knew.
You knew, Susan.
You deserve everything
that's happened to you.
Every fucking thing.
But you know what?
It's behind me now.
I don't give a shit anymore.
[motor revving]
[Susan] You're right.
Your past is behind you.
Right... Right behind you.
Like a shadow.
[in eerie voice] Can't escape it.
Just when you think you're safe.
Healed.
When you breathe a quivering sigh,
my son will be there.
As a husband should.
And he will burn you down
like the whore you are.
You will be dead by dawn!
[grunts]
[groans]
- [Susan grunts]
- [bones cracking]
[ominous music playing]
[Alice chokes]
[growling]
[screams]
[screams, groans]
[gasping]
[groans softly, gasps]
[whimpering]
[whirring]
- [grunting]
- [Susan screams]
[Alice grunts]
[panting]
[intense music playing]
[Joseph] Alice.
Help me up.
I know where the dagger is.
I'll help you find it.
[in eerie voice] And then I'll cut you open with it
like my brother should have.
You're worthless.
Just like my grandfather.
Shut up!
[Joseph] He never found it, and you never will.
Let me end your miserable life.
You like pain anyway.
[Alice screams, pants]
[Joseph] That's why you let Will hurt you.
Isn't it?
Poor little Alice.
[whimpering]
You'll be found in an attic alone.
Gutted from tit to tail.
You never wanted kids anyway.
Your body is useless.
[screams]
[choking, gurgling]
[laughs wickedly]
Wrong one.
- The Circle of the Wise Men is dead.
- [groans]
[ominous music playing]
[Alice grunts]
- [Joseph] Come here, you little bitch.
- [grunts]
I told you it's not here.
- [groans, breath trembling]
- [gasps, exhales softly]
[melancholic music playing]
- [thuds]
- [objects clattering]
[whimpers softly]
[crying]
[creaking]
[ominous music playing]
[screams]
[whimpering]
[wind blowing]
[Alice grunting]
[yelps]
[screams]
[intense music playing]
[whimpering]
[intense music continues]
[Alice panting]
[Susan screaming]
[exhales]
- [whirring]
- [screaming]
[Alice grunts]
[panting]
[intense music continues]
[Edgar] My family will--
Fuck your family!
[whistles]
[breathes softly]
[Elle Etait Si Jolie by Alain Barrière playing]
[music fades]
[thunder rumbling]
[distorted growling]
[panting]
[Will in eerie voice] Did you stay because you liked it?
Or you were
too much of a coward to leave me?
Look at you now.
You still can't leave.
[wind blowing]
Remember the last thing you said to me?
[Will and Alice] "Go to hell."
[Will] You got your wish.
[whimpering]
I shouldn't have hurt you, Alice.
I should have killed you.
[intense music playing]
This is where I promised
I'd always be with you.
[dramatic music playing]
Where I promised that
not even death would do us part.
I will keep my promise, Alice.
'Cause without me,
you are nothing.
[panting]
[dramatic music continues]
[panting continues]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[panting]
[whimpering]
[dramatic music playing]
[walkie-talkie beeps]
[whimpers]
[whispers] Hello?
[radio static]
Hello? Hello--
[La chanson des vieux amants
by Jacques Brel playing on walkie-talkie]
- [music stops]
- [radio static]
[Alice grunting]
[screams]
[gurgling]
[gasping]
[whirring, beeping]
[Alice groans]
[straining]
[dramatic music playing]
[straining, crying]
[Will] I could never have lived
without you, Alice.
I won't let you live without me.
[Alice crying]
[whimpering]
[straining, crying]
[screaming]
[crying]
[softly] Shit.
[screams, grunts]
[Will] Where is the dagger?
Where is it?
Where is it, Alice?
Go get it.
[groaning]
[straining]
[dramatic music continues]
- [grunting]
- [jackhammer whirring]
[screaming]
[Alice whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
[unsettling music playing]
[gasping]
[screaming]
Where is the dagger?
Speak or burn, bitch!
Here's your fucking dagger!
[ominous music playing]
[whimpers softly]
[in normal voice] I love you.
[ominous music continues]
[whispering] That's not enough.
[squelching, cracking]
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music continues]
[Alice groaning softly]
[gasps, crying]
[sirens wailing]
[crying]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Got a cigarette?
- I'm not really allowed to--
- Just give it to me.
Who did this to you?
My ex-husband.
[soft melancholy music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[in normal voice] Wicked little French bitch.
[grunts softly]
- [whimpering]
- Ma'am! What happened? Are you okay?
Oh, thank heaven! Please help me!
She stole my legs!
- [in eerie voice] But yours will do just fine.
- [whimpers softly]
[both screaming]
[ominous music playing]
Yes, sweetie. I know.
It's no fun coming into work
with me on a Saturday.
But I've had to do everything
by myself since--
Well, you know.
I'll make it up to you tonight.
How come you're keeping
all these urns full of dead people?
Uh...
Well... [clicks tongue]
it's sad, actually.
These are the people
whose families never came for them.
So, we keep them here for a few months
in case a family member
remembers to pick them up one day.
[doorbell chimes]
Okay. Don't touch anything, okay?
That might be about the cremator job.
I'll be right back.
"Christopher Leroy."
"Ellie Bixler."
[woman] Hey.
Mom?
[woman] Don't be scared, baby.
[gasps]
[intense music playing]
[roars]
[in eerie voice] Mommy's back.